<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Kellie Lynch</title>
 <link href="http://kellielynch.org/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://kellielynch.org/"/>
 <updated>2012-01-19T21:38:30-06:00</updated>
 <id>http://kellielynch.org/</id>
 <author>
   <name>Kellie Lynch</name>
   <email>kelliedlynch@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Cat Sitting for the Common Man</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2012/01/11/cat-sitting-for-the-common-man/"/>
   <updated>2012-01-11T17:39:43-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2012/01/11/cat-sitting-for-the-common-man</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I wrote this for my stepsister, who was pet-sitting for us over the holidays...mainly because I knew it would annoy her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;The Care and Feeding of the Domestic Feline&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;A Guide for the Common Man&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations! You have joined a long and proud line of temporary companion animal caretakers, known by some as Indentured Servants (Feline), but more commonly referred to as “pet sitters.” While the occupation comes with minimal monetary compensation, the sense of personal satisfaction one can gain from the task is unparalleled, provided the sitter retains all of his or her limbs and mental capacities. This guide will enable you to do just that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Getting to Know Your New Masters&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The animals you shall be serving are known as Nick and Lulu. Nick is a portly fellow with white spots on his chest and paws, and a taste for human flesh. Lulu, a beast of blackest night, tends to be more skittish, but will happily gift you with any disemboweled mice she finds on the premises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both Nick and Lulu enjoy a good scratch atop the head and beneath the chin. Do beware, though, as both animals have a tendency to bare their underbellies, as though in supplication. Under no circumstances should you take this as an invitation to stroke their revealed bellies. Doing so could result in a loss of limbs or life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Scheduling Your Servitude&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cats are fiercely independent creatures, and can be left alone for long periods of time; however, they prefer that their servants check on them once per day. If you cannot manage a daily schedule, visiting them on alternating days will suffice. Your new masters will be satisfied as long as you do not allow two full days to pass between visits. Ignoring them for two days in a row will earn their disapproval, which they may show through sour glares, cleverly-placed piles of excrement, and extreme violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 3&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Way to a Cat’s Heart&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your new masters would prefer to eat tuna fish for every meal. In the absence of tuna fish, they will be happy to subsist on the flesh of their caretakers. If you wish to discourage this behavior, you shall find a dried cereal-like substance that fulfills their dietary requirements in plastic pitchers in the bottom of the pantry. Fill the blue dish carefully, but do not be distressed if some granules escape: the cats consider food from the floor a delicacy, and vastly prefer it to the properly-served food in their dish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 4&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Beverage Selections&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feline companions enjoy the following beverages, listed in order of preference: the blood of the innocent, water from the bottom of the shower, condensation on cold beverage containers, the blood of the not-so-innocent, toilet water, water on the floor, and water in their dish. If you must resort to providing them with water in their dish, rinse the dish quickly and fill it with cold tap water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 5&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Eliminating the Elimination&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cats find human toilets to be beneath them, and as such, prefer to use a box filled with sand, clay, wood pellets, or other grainy substance that can easily be tracked across the floor. To maintain freshness and avoid incurring the wrath of your vengeful masters, the litter box should be cleaned daily. This household uses a three-piece sifting box for quick and sanitary disposal of waste (diagrammed below). It consists of a detachable rim (a), a perforated sifting tray (b), and two solid litter trays (c).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2012/01/litterbox-diagram.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To clean the litter box:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove the detachable rim (a).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lift the top solid litter tray (c), containing the soiled litter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tip the soiled litter into the perforated sifting tray (b).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If any soiled litter remains stuck to the solid litter tray (c), scrape it off with a litter scoop, found underneath the sink. Quickly rinsing the tray may be necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lift the perforated sifting tray (b), allowing the litter to sift through the bottom and into the bottom solid litter tray (c). Solid waste will remain in the perforated sifting tray.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Empty the perforated sifting tray (b) into the trash, and place it inside the empty solid litter tray (c).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Place the full solid litter tray (c) inside the perforated sifting tray (b).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Re-attach the detachable rim.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 6&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Your Very Own Vomitorium&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From time to time, your feline overlords will express their displeasure, discomfort, boredom, or satisfaction by expelling the contents of their stomachs onto the floor. Do not be concerned if this happens as much as once per day; it is completely normal. The resulting messes can be cleaned up with an assortment of household chemicals, found on the shelf above the washing machine, and paper towels, found hanging to the left of the kitchen sink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 7&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;In Case of Emergency&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your benevolent feline masters are hearty, robust creatures, and are unlikely to have any medical problems while under your care. However, if you notice odd behavior, such as the litter box not being used at all, or vomiting 3 or more times in a day, medical treatment may be necessary. During daytime hours, treatment can be provided by the XXXXXXX Animal Hospital at (XXX) XXX-XXXX, and for after-hours emergencies, contact the Animal Emergency Clinic of XXXXXXX at (XXX) XXX-XXXX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: while friendliness and affection can easily be considered “odd behavior,” they are usually not signs of a medical emergency. If a cat is treating you unnaturally well, be on your guard for vicious sneak attacks and excrement left in your shoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 8&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;In Summary&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cats you have been called upon to serve may seem like callous, unfeeling, vicious, petty, scheming, violent, murderous beasts, but that’s how they appear to the untrained eye. If you take the time to get to know them, you’ll see that’s exactly what they are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Armed with this guide, you will be better prepared for the trials that lie ahead. Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Crafty Goals</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2012/01/07/crafty-goals/"/>
   <updated>2012-01-07T19:25:14-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2012/01/07/crafty-goals</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sometimes it seems like all I ever do is re-evaluate my goals and priorities. It's a productive and healthy thing to do on occasion, but I switch directions so often that sometimes I barely recognize myself from one month to the next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wrote a little while ago about &lt;a href=&quot;/2011/09/19/constant-overwork/&quot;&gt;accepting my role as a housewife&lt;/a&gt; and not expecting too much of myself. Once again, I haven't been feeling like I'm accomplishing enough, but this time it's because I'm really not. I started playing WoW again a couple months ago, and since then it's been a rare day that I've gotten through my entire cleaning checklist. The good news is that I've spent the last 3 1/2 weeks out of town, and after that long cold turkey, I find my desire to play is almost nil. I still haven't gotten through the cleaning in the couple of days since I've returned, but that's because I've been unpacking and settling in. I'm okay with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, I still have a strong desire to earn some money. Housewife I may be, but I still want to go on vacations and build up a bigger savings. I've applied for a part-time job near home, which would certainly satisfy that goal, but I have been finding that I also miss the creative outlet that selling on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.etsy.com&quot;&gt;Etsy&lt;/a&gt; provided. I mean, it never really made me money, but it was fun, and it did let me justify buying a whole bunch of craft supplies. That's always a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my new goal is to get &lt;a href=&quot;http://kellielynch.etsy.com&quot;&gt;my Etsy shop&lt;/a&gt; stocked and running again. To that end, I want to do at least one project a week. I've been on a steampunk kick lately, so I'm going to start off with a couple of steampunky projects, but I'll probably also get back into &lt;a href=&quot;/2010/01/03/kindle-cases&quot;&gt;Kindle cases&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/2009/12/10/jubilation&quot;&gt;recycled yarn&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project number one is something I'm probably going to keep, though. It's this vest:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2012/01/vest-before.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I picked this as the first project because it's really simple: I just need to tailor it for a more flattering fit. A couple of darts should do it, and maybe I'll add more buttons. When it's finished, I'll see if it looks good with the rest of my steampunk convention wardrobe...and if not, into the store it goes!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>I Nailed Your Gift</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/12/27/i-nailed-your-gift/"/>
   <updated>2011-12-27T10:46:23-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/12/27/i-nailed-your-gift</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;There's a church near me that has the most unintentionally funny signs I've ever seen, because whoever's writing them doesn't understand the proper use of quotation marks. Last week I was shocked to see one that was funny for another reason. (But it still abused quotation marks, naturally.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2011/12/nailedyourgift.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Man, God is a &lt;em&gt;dick&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sign inspired me to create this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2011/12/jesustree.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I realized as I was finishing it that it could easily be taken as a cynical comment on the modern commercialization of Christmas, rather than the joke I meant it to be. So take it however you like; I'm just glad I finished a drawing.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Another Fresh Start</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/12/23/another-fresh-start/"/>
   <updated>2011-12-23T12:22:23-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/12/23/another-fresh-start</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As I write this, I’m not sure where I’m going to post it. I maintain two separate online identities, neither of which is a fully accurate representation of me. But more on that later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The holidays tend to be a time of introspection for me. I’m currently in Hollywood for a week for my husband’s company Christmas party. I’m not very interested in celebrities, fashion, or spending gobs of money, so that leaves me with little to do while he’s in the office. I find myself with a lot of time for hot baths and writing things like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several months ago, I created a new online identity for myself. I wanted a space where I could talk about controversial topics without worrying about them showing up on a casual Google search of my name. This seems to have caused more problems than it solved, though. My attention is split, and I’m forced to compartmentalize my thoughts for two different venues. Having two different accounts on social media sites makes it more difficult to stay caught up on what my friends and family are up to. My life feels more cluttered, and I detest clutter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On top of that, even under a false name, I have to censor myself. Sure, I can talk about the more salacious details of my life without worry, but because I’m trying to stay anonymous, mundane personal details have to be scrubbed away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m considering abandoning the new identity and only blogging under my real name. It would simplify things immensely. The question, of course, is how much do I value my privacy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I’m not a very private person. If it was just me, I wouldn’t care what details of my life might be out there, but I have a husband and a daughter to consider as well. Part of my motivation was the fear that, if my husband were to lose his job, my eccentricity might hurt him in the search for a new one. Or what if some day we wanted to get our daughter into a fancy private school? If I lay my entire life out there for anyone to see, that leaves my family exposed as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But let’s be realistic: my husband works in web development, a field that tends towards the liberal and eccentric. I have a hard time picturing him being happy at a company that wouldn’t want him just because his wife is a little weird. And as for my daughter...well, the same reasoning applies. I probably wouldn’t want to send her anywhere that would turn its nose up at me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And what of the other looming fear--that some of my more tech-savvy relatives could come across my rants and ruminations and engage me in some very uncomfortable conversations? Well...as time goes on I seem to care about that less and less. Somehow I suspect those conversations would be far more uncomfortable for them than for me, and as such, they’re unlikely to occur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going back to using my real name would still be a big step out of my comfort zone, though. There’s a lot of reassurance to be found in knowing my writing can’t be easily traced back to me. But as I've been discovering, blogging anonymously is a bit out of my comfort zone as well.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Weight Loss</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/11/14/weight-loss/"/>
   <updated>2011-11-14T15:19:56-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/11/14/weight-loss</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I'd say it was about four months ago that I started dieting. I tried low-carb for 3-4 weeks, then went for a more traditional calorie-counting approach. When my husband joined me later, we both started using &lt;a href=&quot;http://loseit.com&quot;&gt;LoseIt&lt;/a&gt; to log food and exercise. After a while, that got frustrating: because he's a guy and he weighed more to start with, his daily calorie allowance was far higher than mine. He got to eat about 30% more than I did, and to make matters worse, he started losing weight and I didn't. After 3 months of jogging and salads, my weight had gone down at most 3 pounds, while he had already lost 20.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weight, of course, isn't the sole measure of a diet's success, but I wasn't seeing a noticeable change in my appearance either--mainly, I suspect, because it was happening so gradually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then a couple weeks ago, I had my first confirmation that it was working. I pulled a pair of pants out of the closet that had been a little tight when I got them. I'd been trying to lose weight at the time and told myself I'd fit into them soon. Well, I didn't. The pants went from &quot;a little tight&quot; to &quot;uncomfortably tight&quot; to &quot;I'm not even going to bother.&quot; So when I pulled them out a couple weeks ago and tried them on for the heck of it, I was absolutely thrilled to find that not only did they fit--they were loose enough that I needed a belt! I didn't notice anything with the pants I usually wear, because I usually wear them with a belt anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then I've been noticing more changes. My face looks thinner. My butt is firmer. I no longer have a muffin-top in my tight workout pants. It feels good to have some confirmation that all my hard work is paying off. I had been on the verge of giving up--now I have no problem getting motivated to go to the gym.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Ancient History</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/10/07/ancient-history/"/>
   <updated>2011-10-07T07:42:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/10/07/ancient-history</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This post has been sitting in my drafts for over a month. Oops. Apologies to my 2 1/2 followers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I've been living in this area for 2 years, and until today hadn't actually looked for a new general practitioner. I finally got the kick in the pants I needed when I contracted strep throat after attending Archon over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was lucky; the first place I called had a doctor who was accepting new patients and had an opening today. I liked her, but I realized as I was talking to her that she was probably younger than I was. It was a little jarring--I know I'm 30, but this is a thing that can actually happen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really don't mind having a young doctor--in fact, I prefer it. I like knowing that medical school is fresh in her memory, and she hasn't had long enough to get too set in her ways. My old doctor in California was about the same age...of course, she was still older than I was at the time I was seeing her. Something about that transition of doctors from elders to peers makes me do a second take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess it wasn't helping matters any that the office was entirely populated by girls who were even younger--fresh-faced buxom young lasses with &quot;student&quot; badges from the local health care trade school. I doubt any of them was older than 23.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stopped at the appointment desk on the way out because I'm long overdue for a physical. When the girl there pulled up my information, she blinked at me. &quot;You're 30?&quot; she asked, incredulous. &quot;You don't look 30.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wasn't sure what to think. On the one hand, I'm happy that I apparently still look young. On the other hand, I'm old enough that a 22-year-old can be shocked at how old I am. (Oh my god, 30? That's, like, ancient! Were people still alive back then?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never thought I'd be one of those people who stressed out about their age. But then again, I never thought I'd be this old, either.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Star Trek Light Bulb Jokes</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/26/star-trek-light-bulb-jokes/"/>
   <updated>2011-09-26T14:59:07-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/26/star-trek-light-bulb-jokes</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've been on a Star Trek kick lately. I've watched the entirety of The Next Generation, and moved on to Deep Space Nine, which I'm now on season 4 of. In the spirit of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bookterra.com/index.php/Bad_Jokes_and_Other_Deleted_Nonsense/Jokebook/Lightbulb/Behavioral#Babylon_5&quot;&gt;Babylon 5 Light Bulb Jokes&lt;/a&gt;, I've been coming up with Star Trek light bulb jokes while I work on the deck. (Which is turning into a bigger project than I anticipated. I want to strangle the house's previous owners who didn't maintain it properly for years.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: How many Bajorans does it take to change a light bulb?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
A: I didn't spend five years in a Cardassian labor camp just to change &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; light bulbs!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: How many Cardassians does it take to change a light bulb?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
A: Two. One to change the bulb, and one to claim it was always lit.&lt;br/&gt;
A: I don't know, why don't &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; tell &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;br/&gt;
A: Just one. &lt;em&gt;[delivered with a smug grin]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: How many Borg does it take to change a light bulb?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
A: One. One to remove the old bulb, one to fetch a new bulb, one to screw in the new bulb, and one to dispose of the old bulb.&lt;br/&gt;
A: Resistance is futile. You will be illuminated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: How many Klingons does it take to change a light bulb?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
A: Why change the bulb? A warrior does not fear the dark!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: How many Vulcans does it take to change a light bulb?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
A: None. It is illogical to use such outdated illumination technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: How many Ferengi does it take to change a light bulb?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
A: One, but if you change them in bulk, he can offer you a &lt;em&gt;substantial&lt;/em&gt; discount.&lt;br/&gt;
A: Three. One to change the bulb for a small fee, one to research the average life of a light bulb, and one to sell you a warranty that expires just before the bulb does.&lt;br/&gt;
A: I'd be happy to tell you...for a small fee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: How many Starfleet captains does it take to change a light bulb?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
A: Three. One to go on the away mission instead of the ship's Lighting Maintenance Officer, one to start a fistfight with whoever broke the old bulb, and one to activate the ship's self-destruct sequence in case the bulb can't be changed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: How many Romulans does it take to change a light bulb?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
A: Five. One to change the bulb, and four to hang around in cloaked Warbirds in case anyone tries anything funny while he's doing it.&lt;br/&gt;
A: I'm not sure--nobody's ever actually seen them doing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don't know why, but light bulb jokes about fictional universes are probably my favorite joke form ever. I am, I admit, a bit of a nerd.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Old Words</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/23/old-words/"/>
   <updated>2011-09-23T21:44:45-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/23/old-words</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I'm working on adding more &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.etsy.com/shop/ChronicDabbler?section_id=10312975&quot;&gt;digital collage sheets&lt;/a&gt; to my Etsy store. Vintage and antique dictionary pages are pretty popular items, and I happened across a 19th century Webster's dictionary for $5 in a thrift shop a while back. Even better, the binding was gone, the pages were yellowing and cracked, and a fair number of them were missing--in that condition, I don't have to feel bad about tearing pages out to scan them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only date I could find in the whole dictionary--1847--was in one of the appendices. One of the things I'm enjoying about this project is seeing how the English language has changed since the mid-1800s. Some words that I consider common are completely absent, others are there but have entirely different meanings, and I keep coming across words that just aren't used anymore. Leafing through this thing is heaven for a language nerd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For instance, the word &quot;date&quot; has absolutely no romantic connotations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2011/09/date.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Courtship was more formalized back then; ladies tended to entertain gentleman callers in their homes, closely watched by a chaperone. No such thing as &quot;dinner and a movie&quot; in 1847. Also on this page, I learned that daughterliness is &quot;the state of a daughter&quot; or &quot;conduct becoming of a daughter.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Halloween coming up in just over a month, this one could be relevant:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2011/09/deadlihood.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Constant Overwork</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/19/constant-overwork/"/>
   <updated>2011-09-19T09:15:46-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/19/constant-overwork</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've been stretched too thin lately, as is usually the case with me. I &lt;a href=&quot;/2011/06/05/mania/&quot;&gt;wrote a bit&lt;/a&gt; about my manic tendencies before, when I was in the process of switching medications to something more appropriate for bipolar depression. I've been on &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lamotrigine&quot;&gt;Lamictal&lt;/a&gt; for about three months now, and while it has curbed the pure giddy &quot;wheee, I can do anything!&quot; moods, it hasn't stopped me from slowly adding more and more projects to my plate until I just can't handle them all anymore. I think it's just become habit; I've been in this state of frantic overwork most of my life, so I feel like a lazy slug if I'm not on the verge of physical and mental collapse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week I finally recognized I'd taken on too much, and I sat down to analyze my projects and obligations. I tried to figure out which ones were most important to me, which ones fit neatly together, and which ones I didn't really enjoy, and only did because I felt I had to. I resolved to stop working on several things entirely, and to quit some others as soon as I'd finished the bit I was currently working on. I came up with a plan for the things that were left; 45 minutes a day on this, 15 a day on that, and I would have time for it all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Problem is, it was still too much. What I failed to realize was that, figuring in things like cleaning, preparing meals, and working out, my &quot;plan&quot; consisted of about 10 hours a day of scheduled obligations, with no breaks or weekends. And so, inevitably, it led to me breaking down once again, full of guilt and self-loathing for not being able to accomplish even my lightened workload.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe the root of my problem is that my end goal for most of my projects is &quot;make money.&quot; Growing up in poverty has led me to feel that one is not contributing to a household unless they're paying bills. So when most of my projects are the sort of thing that require a &lt;strong&gt;lot&lt;/strong&gt; of time and effort to see a profit on--music, art, writing--suddenly my hobbies and passions become daily chores I dread, and I have no downtime, because &lt;strong&gt;everything&lt;/strong&gt; I do is work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, the solution to my problem is to internalize a logical thought process, never an easy task. Our family is extremely fortunate: my husband makes a good enough income that I don't need to work outside the home. The key to my happiness is to embrace my role as a housewife (as much as the teenaged me would have shuddered at the thought), and &lt;strong&gt;truly believe&lt;/strong&gt; that if the house is clean and dinner is on the table, I have done my job. And once my job is done, I can spend my time any way I want. No rigorously scheduled writing time each day--if I feel like writing, I can write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And if, after cooking and scrubbing and mopping, all I really want to do is play video games? &lt;em&gt;That's okay.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>70 Ball Point Pens</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/11/70-ball-point-pens/"/>
   <updated>2011-09-11T21:20:30-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/11/70-ball-point-pens</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2011/09/ball-point-pens.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone's trying to make money by cleaning out their junk drawer. Maybe if I'm lucky, he'll throw in some dried-up white-out and half a roll of Scotch tape.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>War Declared on Mystery Bugs</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/07/war-declared-on-mystery-bugs/"/>
   <updated>2011-09-07T14:27:03-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/07/war-declared-on-mystery-bugs</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Something has been biting us at night, and I have no idea what. It seems most likely that it's either bedbugs or fleas. However, I've thoroughly inspected the mattress and found no signs whatsoever of bedbugs, and the bites aren't in the common &quot;three in a row&quot; pattern that bedbugs usually do. As for fleas, our cats are indoor-only, and they're treated for fleas anyway. I bought a flea comb and combed them several times, and found nothing. No fleas, no eggs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not knowing what we're up against, I've declared war on everything crawly. The mattress is now in a bedbug-proof cover. The carpets in every room have been thoroughly vacuumed and shampooed with near-boiling water. All bedding has been run through a hot wash cycle, and I'm working on the clothes as well. Everything goes into a plastic garbage bag after it's washed, and all the bags are sitting in a non-carpeted room. I sprayed flea spray on every carpet and practically soaked the couch with it. I've ordered some diatomaceous earth and a duster, and plan to apply that stuff to every nook and cranny I can find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was pretty disappointed when, having done all the vacuuming and shampooing and spraying in my bedroom yesterday, I still woke up with new bites today. I finished up the rest of the house today, so if I have bites tomorrow morning...well, we're clearly up against some kind of superbug, and our only hope will be kryptonite, or nuking the house from orbit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the most frustrating thing about all this is not even knowing what I'm fighting. If I could find a bug, or evidence of an infestation, I'd be able to take targeted actions against that specific bug. Currently the only evidence of anything is the bites, and they don't tell me much, apart from that I hate biting bugs.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Little Monsters</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/01/little-monsters/"/>
   <updated>2011-09-01T14:03:02-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/09/01/little-monsters</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I'm about 90% sure that two older children were hitting my two-year-old in the Chick-Fil-A play area today. She came out of a tunnel or slide crying twice, and the older children hid while I comforted her. My daughter doesn't generally cry unless she's hurt or throwing a tantrum, and this definitely wasn't tantrum crying. Then she was acting like she was afraid to go back in the playground until the older children left. On the way out, one of them shook his fist at her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I couldn't very well yell at these kids; they're not mine, and I didn't actually see it happening. And when their mother showed up to take them home, I didn't want to bring it up with her. After all, I don't want to be one of &lt;strong&gt;those&lt;/strong&gt; parents, whose children are always perfect angels while other children are always monsters. There was, after all, a chance that I'd be blaming innocent kids for a couple of totally accidental bumps or trips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, as I held her, her tears soaking into my shoulder, I couldn't shake the feeling I was somehow failing her as a parent. My sweet little girl had been treated unjustly, and I wasn't doing a damn thing about it. I could only stroke her head and tell her that it would be okay.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Manliest Woman in the World</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/08/26/manliest-woman-in-the-world/"/>
   <updated>2011-08-26T16:49:24-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/08/26/manliest-woman-in-the-world</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I just chopped down two trees with a hatchet. I feel like a dangerous dude.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, my wrist did not like that. Ow.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Two Vibrators, Slightly Used</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/08/18/two-vibrators-slightly-used/"/>
   <updated>2011-08-18T22:39:54-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/08/18/two-vibrators-slightly-used</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A few years ago I started collecting absurd classified ads. I had plans for a website, but it turned out I couldn't find enough of them to post several times a week. I figured I might as well post them here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2011/08/two-vibrators.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does one go about buying used vibrators, anyway? Do you get to do a test drive? Oh well, I wanted to get some paintings anyway--might as well kill two birds with one stone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I loved best about this ad was that it ran again a couple weeks later, this time without the miscellaneous household goods. Hope springs eternal.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>An Old Love</title>
   <link href="http://kellielynch.org/2011/08/18/an-old-love/"/>
   <updated>2011-08-18T21:01:21-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://kellielynch.org/2011/08/18/an-old-love</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I'm trying to get back into the theatre. I had my first audition in years today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I flubbed the song pretty badly. I was so nervous that my voice wavered and cracked, and my pitch was off. The director stopped me after the first verse and had me do some scales instead. I screwed up a line early in my monologue, and about three quarters of the way through, my mind went completely blank. I felt the absurd urge to call &quot;Line!&quot; The director had me start over again, but this time with a Jersey accent. My Jersey accent was weak to begin with, and turned into a southern accent after a couple of lines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It. Was. Awful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm glad I did it, though. I need to get used to this if I really want to get on stage again. I've always hated auditions, but then, I'd never done enough of them to get comfortable with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was talk of me perhaps being stage manager, though. I'm excited about the possibility, but I'd be a little relieved if it fell through--rehearsals are nearly an hour away. Still, if I'm looking for a way to get reacquainted with the theatre, this would be ideal...and fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other news, I might have a date on Saturday. I'm meeting someone, but we haven't explicitly stated it's a date. We seem pretty compatible; I suppose if I meet him and find I'm physically attracted to him, I'll unilaterally declare it a date. So there.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
